Guide to the Gary P. and Sandra G. Baden Collection of Print Advertisements, 1840-1986 and undated RL.11193
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Newsprint Materials, 1892-1974; 10
  - Household and Other--Sports celebrity endorsements, 1914-1949 (Box NP11)
  - Miscellaneous unsorted newsprint, 1932-1938 (Box NP11)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes, 1915-1937 (Box NP11)
  - Tourism and Travel, 1913-1940 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Airlines, 1936-1965 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Cruises and cruise lines, 1925-1937 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Destinations, 1919-1938 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Destinations--New York City, 1914-1938 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Destinations--Romania, 1930-1938 (Box NP12)
  - Tourism and Travel--Hotels, 1914-1949 (Box NP12)